hdfclifebuyonline.com 2013-01-15

# HDFC LIfe :: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy:  
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which HDFC Standard Life Insurance Company Limited collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of [www.buyhdfcslonline.com](http://www.buyhdfcslonline.com/) website ("Site").

We may collect personally identifiable information including information that is confidential in nature from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, etc.

Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously i.e. without providing any personally identifiable information but it may be noted that we gather "session information" automatically and use cookies occasionally.We collect personally identifiable information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users are requested to provide information which is current so that the services and facilities offered by us remain relevant and reach the User properly.

We do not assure the User and are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices used by sites/portals links to which may be provided on the Site, although we intend to link only to such sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. Any information we collect from you may be used for a variety of purposes including but not limited to the following:

\- To personalize User experience  
\- To improve our website  
\- To improve customer service  
\- To process transactions  
\- To send periodic emails  
\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
\- To close a sale as well as for post sales information gathering   
\- To communicate with client or for any other post sales requirement

We implement a variety of industry accepted security measures to maintain the safety of the personal information collected from the User by us.

We do not sell, trade or transfer to outside parties your personal information. This doesnot include trusted third parties including our affiliates who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing the User, so long as those parties or affiliates agree to keep this information confidential. The User shall not hold HDFC Standard Life Insurance Company Limited liable for use or disclosure of personal information.

However, we may release your personal information when we believe release is appropiate to comply with the law or legal process, enforce the terms and conditions of products or services including our site policies, to protect us and our affiliates rights,interests or property to protect the interest of others

HDFC Standard Life Insurance Comapany Limited has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed and about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. This policy was last modified on 6.06.2012.
